(Leonard:)Could you tell us?
(Sheldon:)Let's see.
(Sheldon:)Snake eyes. Sorry, bud.
(Penny:)Wait. Hang on. Doubles. Roll again.
(Sheldon:)Okay, get this.
(Sheldon:)It doesn't matter
if he's showering her with gifts...
(Sheldon:)...because the Koothrappalis
are vastly weaIthy.
- What do you mean "vastly weaIthy"?
- Well, "weaIthy" means a lot of money.
"Vastly" means even more.
I'm not sure what's tripping you up.
(Leonard:)I know they have money.
I don't think it's that much.
(Sheldon:)No, you're wrong.
As you know, a few years ago...
(Sheldon:)...I achieved one of my lesser dreams
and became a notary public.
(Sheldon:)Well, from time to time,
I notarize banking documents for Raj.
(Sheldon:)The Koothrappalis aren't just rich,
they're Richie Rich rich.